<div2 id="Common_Attributes-def" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink">
<head>Common Attributes</head>
<p> The following attributes are common to all elements in IDEAL
		</p>
<table border='1' cellpadding='3' width='100%'>
<thead>
<tr>
<th colspan="3">Attributes</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<th>Markup</th>
<th>Purpose</th>
<th>Definition</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr valign='middle'>
<td>id</td>
<td>See http://www.w3.org/TR/2005/REC-xml-id-20050909</td>
<td>
<loc href="http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml-modularization/abstraction.html#dt_ID" xlink:show="replace" xlink:actuate="onRequest">ID</loc>
</td>
</tr>
<tr valign='middle'>
<td>class</td>
<td>This attribute assigns one or more class names to an
				element; the element may be said to belong to these
				classes. A class name may be shared by several element
				instances.</td>
<td>
<loc href="http://www.w3.org/TR/2004/REC-xmlschema-2-20041028/#string" xlink:show="replace" xlink:actuate="onRequest">string</loc>
</td>
</tr>
<tr valign='middle'>
<td>role</td>
<td>The attribute describes the role(s) the current element plays in the context of the document. This can be used, for example, by applications and assistive technologies to determine the purpose of an element. This could allow a user to make informed decisions on which actions may be taken on an element and activate the selected action in a device independent way. It could also be used as a mechanism for annotating portions of a document in a domain specific way (e.g., a legal term taxonomy).</td>
<td>
<loc href="http://www.w3.org/TR/curie/#s_schema" xlink:show="replace" xlink:actuate="onRequest">CURIEs</loc>
</td>
</tr>
<tr valign='middle'>
<td>display</td>
<td>This attribute may be included in any element in the
				document. Its value is a boolean expression. This
				expression may be evaluated by the server, client, or
				other adaptation layer: if it evaluates to 'true' then
				the element containing the display attribute, and all
				its child and attribute nodes, are displayed. If the
				expression evaluates to false, then the element
				containing the display attribute, and all its children,
				are not displayed.</td>
<td>
<loc href="http://www.w3.org/TR/2004/REC-xmlschema-2-20041028/#string" xlink:show="replace" xlink:actuate="onRequest">string</loc>
</td>
</tr>
<tr valign='middle'>
<td>expr</td>
<td>This attribute may be included in any element in the
				document. Its value is a boolean expression. This
				expression may be evaluated by the server, client, or
				other adaptation layer: if it evaluates to 'true' then
				the element containing the expr attribute, and all its
				child and attribute nodes, are selected for inclusion in
				the output document. If the expression evaluates to
				false, then the element containing the expr attribute,
				and all its children, are omitted from the output
				document.</td>
<td>
<loc href="http://www.w3.org/TR/2004/REC-xmlschema-2-20041028/#string" xlink:show="replace" xlink:actuate="onRequest">string</loc>
</td>
</tr>
<tr valign='middle'>
<td>repeat-nodeset</td>
<td>Contains the expression that indicates the source data
				to the repeatig structure</td>
<td>
<loc href="http://www.w3.org/TR/2004/REC-xmlschema-2-20041028/#string" xlink:show="replace" xlink:actuate="onRequest">string</loc>
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</div2>
